A Guide to the Papers of the Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files, (1945) 1967-1982
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files (1945) 1967-1982
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/2/1.841
This collection consists of 3 boxes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection is an archival transfer of the Board of Visitors, Pavillion VIII-East Lawn University of Virginia on 1984 June 21.
Scope and Content Information
Office Administrative files of the secretary of the Board, including: Admissions 1972-1979, Athletics 1967-1975, Bayly-Tiffany Scholorships1968-1971, Conflict of Interest 1981-1982, Development Council 1972, Dormitory Counseling 1970, Excerpts About Minutes 1945-1966, Faculty Mortgages 1969, Hospital 1971-1979, Legal Advisor 1970-1973, memoranda to Board of Visitors, 1981 Nov-1982 May, and Minutes and Excerpts from Correspondence, 1982.
Also newspaper articles 1982, the Rotch Report (on the University Environment relating to the enrollment of black students)1969-1970, 1976, School of Medicine 1970-1978; 1980-1981, Self-Study 1962; 1972-1973; 1975, Staff Assistance Report (By the International Association of Chiefs of Police) 1963-1965, Student Affairs, 1974-1979, and the White Burkett Miller Council -Correspondence 1976 Sept-1979 Dec.
Contents List
- Admissions 1972-1979 (Box 1)
- Athletics 1967-1975 (Box 1)
- Bayly-Tiffany Scholarships 1968-1971 (Box 1)
- Conflict of Interest 1981-1982 (Box 1)
- Development Council 1972 (Box 1)
- Dormitory Counseling 1970 (Box 1)
- Excerpts About Minutes 1945-1966 (Box 1)
- Faculty Mortgages 1969 (Box 1)
- Hospital 1971-1979 (Box 1)
- Legal Advisor 1970-1973 (Box 1)
- Memoranda to Board of Visitors 1981 Nov - 1982 May, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Minutes, Excerpts From [Correspondence] 1982 (Box 1)
- Newspaper Articles 1982 (Box 2)
- Rotch Report 1969-1970, 1976 (Box 2)
  Report of the Committee on Educational and Employment Opportunities, Obligations and Rights. Report on the University Environment - relating to the enrollment of black students.
- School of Medicine 1970-1978; 1980-1981 (Box 2)
- Self-Study 1962; 1972-1973; 1975 (Box 2)
- Staff Assistance Report (By the International Assoc. of Chiefs of Police) 1963, 1965 (Box 2)
- Student Affairs 1974-1979, 2 folders (Box 2)
- White Burkett Miller Council - Correspondence 1976 Sep - 1977 Apr, folders 1-3 of 8 (Box 2)
- White Burkett Miller Council - Correspondence 1977 May - 1979 Dec, folders 4-8 of 8 (Box 3)